<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pixyll</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pixyll</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/posts/00-clojure-development-in-vim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/00-clojure-development-in-vim/</guid>
      <description>Install NeoVim Git clone Pathogen inside of ~/.config/nvim/autoload Git clone the following packages inside of ~/.config/nvim/bundle  Rainbow Parentheses Vim Clojure Static Vim Fireplace  Update your vim file (unlike vim&amp;rsquo;s location ~/.vimfile NeoVim will require the file to be located at ~/.config/nvim/init.vim). Then execute pathogen#infect() which enables Pathogen module loading Turn on the settings for Rainbow Parentheses  au VimEnter * RainbowParenthesesToggle au Syntax * RainbowParenthesesLoadRound au Syntax * RainbowParenthesesLoadSquare au Syntax * RainbowParenthesesLoadBraces  Turn on Clojure Static Navigate to your project in two terminals Start up your leiningen REPL using lein repl In the other terminal start nvim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running An Ubuntu-Powered Terminal In Windows</title>
      <link>/posts/00-native-linux-terminal-in-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/00-native-linux-terminal-in-windows/</guid>
      <description>Intro Lots of time and energy can be spent trying to get a good terminal setup inside of Windows, whether that is using popular tools such as Cywign, cmder, or similar. After trying the various options, the best solution I found was to skip the unnecessaries and use a native Linux shell inside Windows itself! There is a fair amount of setup to get this to work correctly, but buy using the Windows Subsystem for Linux and a native X server running on your Windows machine you can have a nearly seamless experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>